http://www.triumphmusic.com/privacy-statement/

Privacy Statement
At TriumphMusic.com, we respect the privacy concerns of the users and other visitors to our web site. We understand that we are responsible for Personal Information under our control. By visiting TriumphMusic.com, you are accepting the Terms of Use and the practices described in this Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”).
Please review this Privacy Policy periodically. We may update it from time to time and we will notify you of any modifications in this section or in links from this section. Our privacy policy is in accordance with Canada’s Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act (“PIPEDA”).
If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us (at the email or phone number below). “Personal Information” means any information about an identifiable individual but does not include the name, title or business address or telephone number of an employee of an organization.
Information We Collect
For each visitor to this website our web server automatically recognizes non individual data only, but not Personal Information (where possible). We use this information to notify users on updates and optimize the Site for you and to diagnose problems with TriumphMusic.com. We collect information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information, site registrations, and/or orders placed with TriumphMusic.com.
How We Use This Information
We collect the minimum amount of Personal Information necessary to provide our services. The information we collect is used to:
notify users about recent updates on TriumphMusic.com
ship products purchased on TriumphMusic.com and inform buyers about their orders
offer promotional opportunities from us and our partners to site members
improve the function of this website
We do not sell, rent, or lease our site member and customer information to third parties. In order to provide our services, we occasionally share information to our business partners to help make decisions about the content made available to our members. We use trusted, third party companies to assist us in fulfilling orders and processing credit card payments. These companies are only given the necessary amount of Personal Information needed to complete the transaction and payment information is destroyed upon completion of the order. Any transfer of information is subject to the limitations of this privacy statement.
Consent
Personal Information will only be collected, used or disclosed with a site member’s consent, except where required or permitted by law. Consent can be express or implied. It will never be a requirement to obtain a service or product except where necessary to be able to supply that product or service. Site members can withdraw their consent at any time, subject to legal or contractual restrictions. If you would like to withdraw your consent please contact us.
Cookies
TriumphMusic.com uses cookies to help personalize your online experience by, among other things, saving your passwords and preferences for you. These cookies are restricted for use only on TriumphMusic.com, and do not transfer any Personal Information to any other party. If you choose to disable your cookies setting or refuse to accept a cookie, some parts of TriumphMusic.com will not function properly or may be considerably slower.
External Sites
Neither TriumphMusic.com nor its partners are responsible for the privacy practices or the content of external websites. When we include links to other Internet sites, on this site and in our newsletters and other communications, we do so solely as a convenience to our visitors.
Security
We work to secure your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.
Control of Your Information
TriumphMusic.com offers choices to our customers for the collection, use and sharing of Personal Information. If you do not wish to receive e-mail for mailing lists from us you can unsubscribe to the list by using the link at the bottom of every mailing.
Upon request we provide site visitors with access to unique identifier information (e.g. customer number or password), transaction information (e.g. dates on which customers made purchases, amounts and types of purchases), communications that have been directed to our site (e.g. e-mails, customer inquiries), and contact information (e.g. name, address, phone number). Site visitors can access this information through the various account settings features on the website, by writing to us at the email address or the mailing address below. We keep all Personal Information about our visitors up-to-date and encourage our visitors to update us on any changes to their Personal Information by emailing or writing to us.
Privacy Principles for TriumphMusic.com
In addition to anything stated in this Privacy Policy, we abide by the following ten principles:
ACCOUNTABILITY
We are responsible for the Personal Information under our control and have designated one or more individuals who will be accountable for the company’s compliance with the procedures and principles set out in this Privacy Policy.
IDENTIFYING PURPOSE
We will identify the purpose for which Personal Information is collected at or before the time the information is collected. The purposes for which information is collected, used or disclosed by us will be reasonable.
CONSENT
The knowledge and consent of the individual are required for the collection, use or disclosure of Personal Information.
LIMITING COLLECTION
We will limit the collection of PERSONAL INFORMATION to what is necessary for the purposes identified.
LIMITING USE, DISCLOSURE AND RETENTION
Personal Information will only be used or disclosed for purposes we set out. Except with the consent of the individual or as may be required by law. Personal Information will be retained only as long as necessary for the fulfillment of the purposes for which it was collected.
ACCURACY
Personal Information will be as accurate, complete and current as is necessary for the purposes for which it is to be used.
SAFEGUARDS
Personal Information will be protected by security safeguards appropriate to the sensitivity of the information and the circumstances.
OPENNESS
We will make readily available to our users, customers and employees specific information about its policies and practices relating to the collection, use or disclosure of Personal Information.
INDIVIDUAL ACCESS
Upon request, you will be informed of the existence, use and disclosure of your Personal Information and will be given access to that information except in those circumstances that we are permitted or required by law not to disclose Personal Information to the individual. Such individuals will be able to challenge the accuracy and completeness of the information we have and have it changed as appropriate.
CHALLENGING COMPLIANCE
An individual will be able to address a challenge concerning compliance with this Privacy Policy.
Contact Information
If you have questions we are here to help! There are several ways to contact us:
• Email: help@TriumphMusic.com
• Phone: +1 (416) 469-9809 **Please specify your name, order number, phone number, and your question when leaving a message.
• Post: TriumphMusic.com 2238 Dundas Street West P.O. Box 59039 Toronto, Ontario M6R 3B5 Canada
